So, Bitcoin is now at its lowest prices
since Trump got elected, basically.
So, back here, November,
November 5th,
Trump got elected. I mean, we got the
pump, but we're right back down to those
prices. Um, so here's where I'm at with
it.
You guys aren't going to want to hear
this, but I've been buying. Um,
I say you're not going to want to hear
that because I know a lot of you guys
probably aren't buying.
Um, I know it's hard to buy, especially
when it keeps going down. It's like,
man, why I'm buying? It's going down.
Um, but
that's always what I wish I did when we
have runups and when the bull market
comes back around. I'm wishing that I
wasn't fooling around with altcoins and
stuff and just stacking Bitcoin,
stacking Ethereum.
and last cycle stacking Salana.
So,
I've been buying every single day. I
started buying
I would say I think it was back around
here 83.
And I made a vow that every time, well,
not even every time, but every day I'm
going to buy the same amount of well
take the same amount of fiat and buy
crypto with it. The same through cryptos
every single day. And I even did a
calculation on how much I would spend if
I just did that.
And on top of that, on days like today
where it's kind of going parabolically
down, I buy more than I would have
bought.
So, um,
yeah. And I guess you want some reasons
why. Here's why. So, if you've been
watching my members content for the past
couple of months or weeks for this um
metric, but if you've been watching,
I've been talking about the Bitcoin
electrical cost. Um this is basically
the cost to mine one Bitcoin.
Now, what you'll notice about instantly
notice about this chart is that we never
go we may go below it, but it doesn't
stay around this red line long. And that
red line is now at 58,000. Now, it does
go up and down, but it trends up.
So,
this is the full chart. This is the free
version. um it has a three-week delay on
it, but we can see that every time and
if we, you know, guess you could count
this, but still the same rings true. If
it's near this line, you should be
buying it.
So, this is one of the new indicators
that I've thrown into my repertoire on
top of the Bitcoin stock to flow, which
I don't really follow the stock part or
the stock toflow part. I more measure
the days until having. That's the only
thing that I focus on with this chart is
the fact that when we're turning green,
you want to start accumulating. You
don't want to say, "Okay, I'm going to
wait till it's green and then start
buying because if you do that, you've
missed all the buying and now you're
going to end up buying higher as we go
into the having." So, this has been true
the entire time I've been in crypto.
This has been true. So,
I'm going to start buying now. I'm not
I'm ignoring all the
the Steen, you know, all the Steam FUD.
We'll call it the Steam FUD, all the um
Trump FUD, all the banker FUD, all the
dollar FUD. I'm ignoring all of that
stuff
cuz there's so much of it right now. All
the gold FUD, silver FUD, Peter Schiff
FUD. Like, it's it's so hard. It's so
easy to find FUD now, right? Fear,
uncertainty, and doubt. It's so easy to
find that stuff now. It's really hard to
find content like this that's buying.
There's a few out there, but it's not
hard to find people like me. So every
day, no, I mean I I don't want to say no
matter what, but it's if I can get to
some internet,
you know, I'm going to try and buy the
same three coins
every day.
I don't like looking down because, you
know, when you're looking down at prices
and when people start throwing out
predictions lower, it's usually around
the bottom. So I don't want to be
looking down here. But I'm going to go
ahead and say if I was going to predict
something, I think we're going to come
to this support right here. This is
going to be around that electrical cost.
And if we look back, we can see this is
a pretty critical support line going all
the way back to here back in 2018, the
bottom of 2018.
So through COVID, I mean, I wouldn't
measure this one, but I would measure
the closes here. It lines up with this
one, and it stretches all the way up to
here. And I think we're going to meet
it.
Hopefully we meet it over here. You
know, that would be nice. But I think
we're going to at some point meet this
cuz I'm looking at that. I'm sure a lot
of it's I'm sure a lot of other
indicators are lining up with that. Like
if I throw in this, let's see, seven.
No, that one's not.
Anyway, but I'm sure if I zoom Oh, this
is the daily chart. Let's go to the
weekly, right? We can see the 200 on the
weekly is lining up with about that
level. So, I'm sure, like I said, this
support line is going to show up on
multiple indicators and smart money is
looking at that area for
a bottom and a long position. Also,
another thing that's looking good is I
would much rather I love seeing stock
RSI down here in all scenarios if I'm a
bull. So, it's good to see this is
getting down here. So, that means we're
getting due for a up move. And I bet you
as soon as that up move comes, the
inevitable green candle, the entire X
feed is going to turn bullish.
Everybody's going to talk about how they
were buying the whole time and all those
bears are going to disappear.
So whenever
I'm thinking it's here, I'm thinking the
ultimate FUD is going to be
since Trump didn't do it, Steam didn't
do it, I think it's going to be Michael
Sailor. Something's going to go happen
with him and it's going to crash and
we're going to wick
below here and it's going to be really
scary.
But you just got to remember
that
Bitcoin always recovers, man.
It's versus the dollar. I mean, if only
way is if like the dollar stops being
printed,
which you know, they could definitely
slow it down, but the inevitable is you
got to print some more dollars. So,
that's what I'm thinking.
If we crash below here and stay below
here,
then it must be really bad. Something
happened. Something broke. But the era
that we're going in,
think about all the stuff that they've
been saying this whole time, man. How
bullish the world is on crypto.
And now all of a sudden, we're going
back to gold and silver.
the dollar strong, you know, stuff like
that. Like, come on, man. Do I look like
an idiot to you
world?
You guys just had me convinced that
crypto is taking over the world. And it
it is like store big companies are
starting to accept bit. I think Walmart,
I mean, I don't think they're accepting
Bitcoin as the currency, but you can use
it now. Stake and shake. There's some
news about Stake and Shake. They
actually started taking Bitcoin a couple
years ago and now they're reporting back
and saying that their business started
doing better once they started accepting
Bitcoin. So crypto is here to stay. It's
the feed, your X feed and all of that
that's making you doubt it. So um
like if you really think about it, the
dollar is so inflated, right?
It's so inflated, but prices are going
down on this stuff. So, what does that
mean? Like, you want to buy this stuff
when it's going down. When things are
going down in price, there's not much.
Put it like this. There aren't many
assets that are going down in price. So,
if you find some assets that are going
down in price, maybe buy them. You know,
it's kind of simple. It's kind of common
sense. Like when gold was ripping and
silver was ripping a couple days ago,
it's because of the dollar. Well, then
why is Bitcoin falling? And if Bitcoin
is falling, maybe we should be buying
it. You see what I'm saying? So, and I
just use Bitcoin as the standard as the
you could I mean, I wouldn't say it for
every crypto, but I say it for Bitcoin,
Ethereum, Salana, B&B,
Tron, which is still at 27 cents. It
hasn't really failed, but it's looking
pretty shaky, actually. Like, yeah, that
looks kind of bearish, not going to lie.
Finally.
Um, and maybe that's a bullish sign for
the rest of crypto. Like, if Tron's
about to be falling, man, everything
else must be about to rip.
So, that's where I'm at with some of you
guys are wondering what are some other
things I'm doing to diversify.
Before I get into that, I had another
thought. When I posted my post about me
taking profit at the top back in a
August, giving my reasons on why I'm
taking profit on ETH, BTC, and anything
else that trended up from there. 46,000
4,600 for ETH. I expected this post to
be met with a lot of, "Oh man, you're an
idiot. You're stupid. It's going to go
so much higher." But looking back,
what's interesting about this post is
everybody was like, "Yeah,
well, this guy's being funny. This time
is different." But most people were
like, "Yeah, it's a good idea. Valid
point. I ain't mad at that call." Top,
you know, everybody was like, "Yeah,
you're right.
Nobody really fought." And what's
interesting is let's fast forward to now
where I posted a video of me buying
starting at 77. Let's see what the
comments were saying.
Not really seeing anybody
here. Somebody saying saying lower 50k.
Um,
feels good. These prices taking a
beating, huh? But wait a while, you can
get it. So, it's still a little bit of
people still saying lower. And that's
interesting as well. So, I'm thinking
when I say
that the bottom is in and everybody is
like, "Yeah, me too. I'm buying." Yep.
Yeah. It's probably not going in much
lower. It's probably the bottom because
it looks like my audience,
you know,
if I'm wrong, they'll let me know. If
I'm when I'm right, they're like,
"Yeah." So,
I'm not ready to call a bottom yet.
Um, but hey, it'd be cool if it was the
bottom, right? But I'm thinking
I'm thinking this right. This is just
calling my name. This area right here is
just the 200, you know, then it lines
right up with this the electrical cost.
You know, this area wherever this this
line
meets us the price at that's the bottom.
Maybe a wick below. Maybe it
teeters on it for a little while.
Um
but yeah, so what are some other things
I'm doing?
who diversify, not really so much as
make money, but diversify
long term.
One of the things that I'm having fun
with and have had fun with for the past,
I would say five years off and on and a
little bit when I was a kid was trading
cards. Now, I'm sure a lot of you, maybe
a lot of you haven't, but some of you
might have heard that Pokemon is going
nuts. Like, if you have Pokemon from
like 2016 or or any poke any Pokemon
from 20 pre2020,
you know, you're way up.
Um, so Pokemon is going nuts, but that's
not what I'm buying. Funny enough, what
I'm buying is sports cards.
I think relative to Pokemon, sports
cards are really undervalued.
One, because they're real people. Now, a
lot of people say, "Well, I like Pokemon
because it's not real people. It's
Pokemon Pikachu is not going to get
hurt. He's not going to get injured."
But, you know, you can buy players that
are already goats like Kobe,
Jordan, LeBron. I think it's a little
bit early on or late on him. And I think
he has too much stuff. I could go on and
on. And it's so parallel with crypto
because it is so reliable on scarcity
and how many cards they printed that
year and the condition of the card and
what grade it got and how many
cards are in that condition.
You know, the rarity of sports cards is
way higher than Pokemon.
Um, [clears throat]
like this one right now. This is Drake
May. He's in the Super Bowl this Sunday,
so his stuff is going crazy. You know, I
had some Drake May at the beginning of
the year. Um, I still have a little bit
of Drake May stuff, but not what I had
before the season. So, if you're into
like trading
and want to speculate,
sports cards is where it's at. If you
want a new thing to if you're into
sports even a little bit, it makes
sports so much more fun because now
you're actually it's better than
gambling on the player, you know, or
gambling on the game like Drake May.
Let's look at his chart.
So, I mean, this is a very low
definition chart, but
you can see he came out hot. This is
back 2025 when he first when these cards
first came out. So he had a pretty
decent season last year. And then you
can see that when football ends when
after the Super Bowl these players cards
start to roll over. So there's a buying
opportunity for when in the offseason.
So last year what I did is I did just
that. I bought some Drake May cards. I
bought some Jaden Daniel cards. I put
made a list. I put all the rookies in a
list. And then I bought Bo Nicks, JJ
McCarthy, P. I bought all these guys.
This is a car that I pulled out of a out
of like a $700 box. And I sold this car
for 4600. Here's my sale. My sale is
actually on this list. It was this one
right here. I sold it the top.
So I bought all these guys and then
before the season starts, well before
the season started, I sold his stuff.
So, I bought the stuff down, bought
these cards down here around April, May,
and then I sent them off to get graded
and when I got the grades back, I went
to a card show and I sold them back in
August. Now, of course, I should have
kept his cards because I mean, he's in
the Super Bowl, but it's probably not
going to happen. Like, let's look at
somebody like Spencer Rattler. I bought
his stuff over the during the offseason.
So, same thing with him, which is buy
his cars and then sell them going into
the season and it's been down ever
since.
That's how most players do, but there's
a window of opportunity every season.
It's a cycle. It's the same thing that
we're already in. So, I mean, I really
don't even want to show y'all this. I
mean, I do because it's what I'm into
and it's what I want to talk about. But
yo, I could just chill over here and
play that game while buying like a Kobe
card and sitting on it. Let's go to
Kobe.
So, Kobe has a few rookie cards because
they were making a good amount of cards
back then. So, he has a good selection
of of rookie cards. The main rookie card
is the Kobe Bryant Top Scrum.
It's this one,
right?
Yeah. 1996 top chrome
PSA 10 for the base. Now, it's different
levels. The main one that everybody
would want are the refractors. is a
refractor in PSA 10 is 97. Last sold for
97,000 on a low. It went up to 117, but
it's on a dip now. Let's look at the
alltime chart for this. It's down.
It's down from 500K.
So, what I like about sports cards is
just like gold, you can pack a lot of
value in something the size of a card.
So when you can put it in your pocket,
it's almost it's almost like crypto
almost
because it's so small and it's so
portable.
Now
I strive to get one of these. Maybe I'll
start with the base. I mean, it's going
to go up. I mean, it could be on a dip
now cuz it's been on a run. So, I'm
trying to hold back on buying some of
this stuff, but there are cars out there
that are like
pumping. Like one, like a good example
is Steph Curry. Now, Steph Curry is
still alive. He's still pretty young. He
could still have something happen. He
could have some scandal or something.
And we all just say, "Oh, [__] him." You
know, we find out he's like Epstein
Island or something.
>> [laughter]
>> then it's over. But his card, the
interesting thing about him is he's from
2011, I think.
No,
the interesting thing about his cards is
in 2009, sports cards and cards in
general weren't popular. So, they were
making less of them. They weren't
printing as many as they are now. Like
right now, cards are more popular than
ever. So, it's probably kind of toppy on
this new stuff. So, you don't want to
hold this new stuff like Drake May and
stuff. They're making a ton of it. But
his cards, if I go to, let's see, PSA
10, there's only 371 of these base
cards. Like, I'm sorry, I know this
stuff so y'all don't know it, but
there's only 200 371 base cards in a 10.
That's why it's so expensive. That's not
even counting the refractors and the
chromes and all that. That's just simple
basic card. I mean, if this was anybody
else, this is like a 99 cent card.
Anybody else?
And if you compare that to somebody like
let's go to the guy, the the the big guy
right now, Wimby,
his rookie card, look, 26,555
of his PSA 10 base card
and they're going up.
There's way too many of them.
So, there are opportunities in
this space as far as diversifying. And
I've been doing it for allegedly
the past 5 years, but not really as hard
as I wish I would have been going.
But now I'm
starting to be like, "All right, it's
time to maybe store some value in some
other places."
So I'm, you know, keeping it simple.
Jordan,
you know, his stuff is fairly cheap
because when they were making his stuff,
it's the same thing. Sports cars are
really popular. this era from like 1985
888 somewhere around in the late 80s to
the early 90s they were printing a [__]
ton of cards because it was really
really popular. So his stuff is really
cheap. So you if I mean Vic I don't
think Victor win is going to be the next
Jordan but his stuff is going to be
relatively cheap you know 20 years from
now. Kind of like Jordan's. Now, what
you notice about Jordan stuff though is
when it gets to the later 90s, when they
start slowing down as far as how many
cars they're making, those ones are more
expensive. So, those are the ones that I
kind of go after, like the late 90s.
Let's try and find one. I mean, this
isn't one, but this is one of my I I
have this car right here. It's a cheap
one, but jumping. I mean, I I like the
picture for me with Jordans. I like when
he's doing Jordan in the photo. If he's
doing Jordan in the photo, like
something like this, this is cool. I
don't have this, but this is cool. But
it's not really him, you know? Or if
he's wearing the shoes, like I'm really
big on what shoes he has on. If he's
dunking, like there's one I bought the
other day. I don't remember the name of
it, but um the Jordans and he's dunking
with these Jord the twelves on.
Here's a Tops. Which ones? The 11s.
decent.
But, you know, you can get one of these
for pretty cheap. You can get a 10 for
149. So, I'm past this part now. I'm
like, this is what I was doing. I was
buying these and they went up. Like, all
of my cards are up, too. It's funny.
Like, that's that's the portfolio that's
at new highs. My sports cards, funny
enough.
So,
yeah. I wouldn't say it's too late,
though. I think, you know, PSA 10, it's
only 1,900 of them, so it's not that
much of it. But the pe the the
generation that's on him right now is
kind of older. So I think he's kind of
already priced in. So what I'm doing now
is I'm trying to go back in my
generation and the generation after me.
Who are they going to be nostalgic over?
They're going to be nostalgic over Kobe,
Steph Curry, LeBron, etc. And I'm just
I'm just talking basketball. Football
might end up being actually the one that
that's what I'm actually betting on is
football. I've already kind of I'm doing
basketball, too, but I think football is
the sleeper because football is more
popular than basketball right now. So,
they'll probably be more nostalgic over
football players like Aaron Rodgers,
Brett Favre, Tom Brady, who I don't have
any Tom Brady. Like, his stuff is just
always going up. Um,
who else? I can't really think right
now.
Patrick Mahomes. I think it's a little
bit too late on him. Should have bought
his stuff a long time ago.
Um, but people like that. They're going
to be He'll probably cool off though.
Like his stuff should be down now,
actually. Low key. Patrick.
Here's his rookie right here. $153 for
his base card raw without a grading on
it. That's kind of wild.
So PSAT 10 base. Damn, that's crazy.
So yeah, then you But it's so many
parallels. That's the difference between
now and in the past. Like they make so
many different variations of the card,
you know? So get the press proof blue.
It's only 30 of those. So you'll be
lucky if there's even one for sale.
So you kind of got to just go by what's
available to be bought. So, what I do is
I go to copy this.
You know, it's kind of how I do it.
Like, I might end up buying Patrick
Mahomes today. You know, I sit around, I
think about, huh, who do I who who is a
sleeper right now? Patrick Mahomes.
Didn't he get hurt or something? So, I
type in Patrick Mahomes. I take this two
out.
Rookie card.
I like auctions,
you know. These are not rookies. 2025 20
and I'll say this is a little hack right
here. Minus025
is these rookies 2017. I get this rookie
year. Verify. Yeah, 2017
is his rookie year.
And what do we got?
[snorts and clears throat] Let's go.
Ending soonest with bids.
Yikes.
Not even greatest. It's $70 with one day
left. It's hardly anything even
being auctioned off.
It's insane, bro.
Like, this is the best bet.
Now, what I do is I look at it and I
look at the corners.
It's pretty sharp. Edges look sharp.
Uh, look at that right there. See,
that's kind of dinged right there. I
don't I don't like that corner.
So now what I do, I'm giving y'all to
play. [__] it. Cuz y'all ain't going to
do it anyway. Y'all don't care about
this. And I type in I copy this. Then I
go to this site 130 point.
And then I was buying some LaMelo
for the PC,
my personal collection.
and we'll see how much this car sold for
previously. 500. That's for sale right
now.
Um,
has there even been any of these?
What is it?
Stellar Star Silver rookie.
This is probably a pretty rare one.
Let's throw it in market movers.
Stellar stars. There we go. 130 on.
Okay. So, not bad, but that corner is
atrocious. So, I don't I'm not
interested in that.
[snorts] Let's see. We got
That's about it for today. Just this
one. This isn't
these aren't rookies.
Uh yeah. Yeah. And I just try and find
something that people might be sleeping
on.
I think buying Patrick Mahomes. Let's
see now. Let's see.
Base. And I can I go off the market by
looking at their base cards.
[snorts] Okay. So, let's see. He's on a
dip right now
because he didn't go to the playoffs.
So, now is opportunity to be like not
chasing it. You don't have to worry
about if if you're chasing it or not.
170 166.
Let's see if any of these are for sale.
So, right now they going for 180. I can
get this one for 180.
Okay, here's one. So, why I didn't see
this one on there?
This one's already at 160. So, you're
not going to get like a steal on one of
these cuz there's too many people
watching.
Why is this one going for 88?
Those edges look horrible,
you know? So that's why I kind of just
try and stick when it when it's this
level like I just try and get like a PSA
and call and then I can just say I have
one
and I think it's I don't know even in
the like even if it's in a nine I still
want it to look you know it's levels it
still look at the whiting on it like
it's not it's not perfect man it's not
close enough to perfect it's probably
why it's the cheapest one. I mean ain't
probably that is why it's the cheapest
one.
Um [groaning]
let's look at this one. 325.
Sometimes it's the light that's shining
and make it look like it's got some bad
edges. So you got to be
a little bit of white right there. Like
for me it's like could I crack this out
of here and rescend it and it possibly
get a 10? Because if I did that then
boy,
you know, if I if I crack this out of
here, bought it for 325, crack it out
and send it back and it gets a 10, you
know, that's a come up.
But, you know, I probably wouldn't do it
with one of these. You could do it with
cheap newer cards though, easily
like Caleb Williams. I'm trying to think
sh I'm trying to hold out until like
April, May for Caleb Williams. and
[clears throat] these guys, Michael
Pennix,
Jayen Daniels.
Wait for these to cool off cuz they're
kind of up right now because people were
like, "Oh, I'm going to buy him before
the season starts." So, he's on a little
bump right now. But, I think by the time
like April
rolls around, it might be back down or
cooling off.
But, um, these you can kind of do it
easier. This one 149. You find one
that's in that looks like it should be a
10 in the picture. It's like there's
nothing wrong with me. It's a little bit
of,
you know,
and then on the black right here, like
there's no white on this black right
here. Oh man, it's looking this one is
looking clean. A little bit of something
there, but yeah, this is I'll probably
pass on that one. But, you know,
get it. Send it back in. Get a 10.
People do that with Pokemon. Pokemon to
me is just too
too pumped right now. It's too viral.
Oh, another thing I do sealed boxes.
So,
I bank on these sealed boxes that have
the cards still in them and they're
sealed. And these go up
to this one I bought. This is like my
best buy so far on some Seal Wax. I got
this one for like 300. I don't remember
when, but I want to say like right in
here somewhere.
And it's been going up ever since. They
all go up. Some go up more than others.
Others because of like this one right
here, 2017. We know who's in 2017.
Patrick Mahomes. Look at the box.
$11,000 for one. And it's pumping.
You know, for a box of cards, guys,
it's not a game out here. It's not a
game.
Basketball is even crazier.
You want to box with us some cards? You
want to box with uh who is this? I think
this is the one that has um what's the
first year prism?
You know,
there's nobody really in basketball
right now besides LeBron. Here's the
latest season. Cooper flag. Look at
that. Just up and up and up and up and
up. Now, the thing is,
I don't think these things are over. You
would be like, "Man, that's expensive."
But I don't think these things are
overvalued
because I've been watching it for so
long and I'm like, "Yeah, this these
things are actually kind of cheap
[laughter]
if you really think about the whole
thing about like collecting and how
bigger things are getting. like things
are becoming easier to know about like
so I can't really explain it but
cars from the 2010s I think are next up
like 2005
to 2015 like I'm trying to get stuff in
that era that's the cheap stuff low key
like that's the gym is if you can find
like
basically sleeper players is like Aaron
Rogers his stuff. Let's see how his
stuff is doing. I mean, it's a boring
See, that's a boring name right now. You
know what I'm saying? Like, but he's
going to be the goat. He's going to be
one of the goats in
when people start looking back when he's
out of the league and people start
looking back at him.
2005.
What's Tops?
Let's do Tops Chrome.
$90. It's not bad.
Base refactor 475. Like, it's a lot, but
it's really not.
like this is easily, you know, I'm
thinking 10x on everything from the
early 2000s. 10x. That's kind of how I'm
looking at it. It's like, yeah, this is
a 10x and probably not that long from
now. Like, this is easy 4,000
for raw refractor. We just seen that,
you know, that's Steph Curry.
The same time period,
early 2000. Let's see how many of them
are there. 13 PSA 10s, bro. It's only 13
of them shits. You be lucky to find one.
There's not. You ain't going to find
one.
Now it's 199 of them [__] I'm on to
something. I ain't selling y'all [__]
up. Good luck out there.
Look at the chart. [clears throat]
Yeah, I'm thinking what it is. This is
the kind of charts that we want.
Let's look at a Pokemon now. Let's go.
Let's compare the Pokemon
cuz that's what I was about to get into.
Let's go. Let's go and get in the time
machine. Let's go back. So, right now,
the big one is Evolving Sky. Like,
Evolving Sky is 2,000 a box. Like, it's
kind of I mean,
it's cheap, but
it's kind of different because it's
Pokemon. Like it's not I don't think
it's as rare. I think the boxes of the
cards that I showed are much more rare
than these. Like it's not hard to find
this stuff. There's always plenty of
people selling evolving skies,
you know. Um,
but as far as like a card, let's think
of um let's just go Charizard,
you know, the the the the North Star
[clears throat]
Charizard. Um, it's the uh main one.
What's it called? Base.
Base set.
Okay, we'll just go with this one right
here. Base set, too. I don't really
know.
Okay, this one isn't going back as far
as I wanted to for some reason.
Well, we're still not as This is the
Japanese, but it's still a good
indicator. We're not as parabolic as
2020 COVID, but I do think that we get
past those COVID levels for cards in
general. And I think if you can get
something that's not doing this, which
is Pokemon, I mean, Kobe's stuff is
doing is pumping already, but I think
stuff like Aaron Rogers,
you know, Ben Rothlessberger,
I don't know. You know, I think if
there's another big bubble, those are
going to go up more basically than
everything else. Dwayne Wade and it
started Dwayne Wade for some reason.
Like [snorts]
that era.
Here's top scroll. There it is. Look at
that. $10. It's base refactor 270. It's
not bad.
It's not pumping.
It's up. But basketball season is is in.
So it's kind of like it's not a good
time to buy basketball or football
really. It's not really. You're kind of
probably overpaying.
But yeah, that's just something else
that I'm into. I mean, I'm really into,
as you can see, like it's crypto and
this
for me. Like, I'm got if I'm going to do
something and that's monetary, I got to
love it. I can't be in stuff that's just
not interest. I'm just doing it for
money. Um,
so yeah, if this is something you're
interested in, let me know. I'll do more
content on it. Um, maybe I'll start
showing, you know, the things I bought
that week, stuff like that. Let me know.
Talk to you on the next one. Peace.